itradecimb.com.sg 2012-10-30

# i*Trade@CIMB SG - Privacy

CIMB Securities (Singapore) Pte Ltd ("CIMB") takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn about our Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of 19 February 2001. CIMB reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by publishing the new Privacy Policy on the Website (as hereafter defined). This Privacy Policy and the statements outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.   
  
---  
**1.** | **What this Privacy Policy Covers**  
1.1 | 

This Privacy Policy covers how CIMB uses the personally identifiable information (the "Personally Identifiable Information") it collects. However, please note that this Privacy Policy only applies to the website at Internet URL www.itradecimb.com.sg and [my.itradecimb.com.sg](https://my.itradecimb.com.sg/) (the "Websites") and does not apply to the websites owned and/or operated by third parties.  
  
1.2 | 

CIMB is not responsible for any actions or policies of third party websites which are hyperlinked to and from the Website. You should check the applicable privacy policy of such party before providing Personally Identifiable Information to such websites.   
  
**2.** | **Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**  
  
2.1

| 

This Privacy Policy covers how CIMB uses the personally identifiable information (the "Personally Identifiable Information") it collects. However, please note that this Privacy Policy only applies to the website at Internet URL www.itradecimb.com.sg and [my.itradecimb.com.sg](https://my.itradecimb.com.sg/) (the "Websites") and does not apply to the websites owned and/or operated by third parties

(a)  apply to be a registered user of the Website;   
(b)  when you visit the web pages on the Website that can be accessed without the need for   
      registration;   
(c)  when you enter promotions or contests that are available to you without having to be a   
      registered user of the Website;   
(d)  when you use the online services available on the Website (the "Online Services"). 

    CIMB also automatically receives and records information from your browser on our server logs including but not limited to your Internet protocol address, cookie information and the page you requested  
  
2.2 | 

CIMB uses the Personally identifiable Information:

(a)  to facilitate your access to the Website or your use of the Online Services;  
(b)  to customize and personalise the content of the web page that you see;   
(c)  to fulfill your requests for the Online Services; and   
(d)  to evaluate your preferences and facilitate future works on the Website.  
  
**3.** | **Information Collection and Use**  
3.1 | 

Your Personally Identifiable Information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without your approval at the time of collection. At such point of collection, you will have the opportunity to indicate whether you would like to "opt out"of receiving promotional and/or marketing information about other products, services and offerings from CIMB and/or any third parties.  
  
3.2 | 

However, CIMB reserves the right to contact you regarding matters such as account status, changes to the subscriber agreement and other matters relevant to the Online Services and/or the Personally Identifiable Information collected.   
  
3.3 | 

CIMB also reserves the right to perform statistical analysis of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. CIMB may sell or provide aggregated data from these analysis to third parties  
  
3.4 | 

Except as provided in paragraph 3.3, CIMB will not sell or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to anyone.  
  
3.5 | 

CIMB will send Personally Identifiable Information about you to other companies or people when: 

(a)  We have your consent to share the information;   
(b)  We need to share your information in order to provide the Online Services or other services   
      that you have requested; and   
(c)  We are compelled by any law, court order, legal process or regulatory authority to disclose   
      your Personal Identifiable Information to third parties.  
  
**4.** | **Cookies**  
4.1 | 

"Cookies" are small text files a website can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the website and allow a website to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising. Cookies are not programs that come onto a user's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site.  
  
4.2 | CIMB may set and access CIMB cookies on your computer   
4.3 | 

CIMB allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. The use of cookies by such companies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to CIMB's cookies.   
  
4.4 | 

If you do not want any information about yourself to be collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature. However, please note that if you do this, certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the Website may not be available to you.
